**IESHA NELSON** 

166 Southern Main Road, Fyzabad, Trinidad and Tobago.

Cell: 1-868-333-6914

Email: Iesha.nelson25@gmail.com

May 24th 2014

**HILO FOOD STORES** 

Manager, Recruitment & Employee Welfare "FILING OFFICER" #39A Wrightson Road

Port of Spain.

Dear Sir/Madam,

I am writing to apply for the advertised position of FILING OFFICER within your

establishment.

I am inquisitive, energetic and easily self-motivated motivated individual. My experiences

gained through academics, sports and in the workplace, lend to and have developed my ability to

work individually as well as within a group, to multitask, to effectively communicate, and to

maintain strict working relationships and confidentiality. I am computer literate and I'm certain

that any task which involves the usage of software such as Microsoft Excel, amongst others, I

can satisfactorily complete.

Thanking you in advance for your kind consideration. I am eagerly awaiting your response. Hope

to soon make your acquaintance. Hope to soon make your acquaintance.

Yours respectfully,

**IESHA NELSON** 

## **IESHA NELSON**

# 166 Southern Main Road, Fyzabad, Trinidad and Tobago.

Cell: 1-868-333-6914

Email: <u>Iesha.nelson25@gmail.com</u>

# **OBJECTIVE:**

To obtain the FILING OFFICER position within your establishment.

# **EDUCATION:**

•	University of The West Indies	St. Augustine
	- Bachelor degree in Science	2010 - 2014
	Major: Geography	
	Minors: Environmental Physics	
	Electronic Physics	
•	Fyzabad Anglican Secondary School	Fyzabad
	- A'Level Cape	2008 - 2010
	Units 1 & 2: Geography	
	Mathematics	
	Physics	
	Communication Studies	
	Caribbean Studies	
	- 9 CXC O'level Passes	2003 - 2008
	Mathematics (Grade 1 with distinction)	
	English (Grade 2)	

## **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:**

Place	Position	Date
Center for Language learning,	Assistant technician	2010 - 2013
UWI, St. Augustine.		

## **CO-CURRICULAR/VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE:**

ctivity		Date
•	Fyzabad Anglican Secondary School's	2009 - 2010
	ACT OF KINDNESS (AOK) charity club President	
•	Fyzabad Anglican Secondary School's	2008 - 2009
	ACT OF KINDNESS (AOK) charity club Treasurer	
•	School Prefect of Fyzabad Anglican Secondary School	2008 – 2010
•	Vice-House Captain at Fyzabad Anglican Secondary School	2008 – 2009
•	Tennis Team Member	2008 - 2009

## **ADDITTIONAL SKILLS:**

# **Technical and Computer literacy**

- Multi-media operation.
- Microsoft Word, Excel and PowerPoint.
- Geographic Information Technology
- Some experience with Seismic Sensing.

## **REFERENCES:**

#### • Ms. Yakira David

House Officer Eric Williams Medical Sciences Complex Mount Hope Cell #: 787 – 6329

## • Mr. Joel Billy-Taitt

Headman Winchman Well Servicing Petrotrin Santa Flora Tel#: 648 – 0765 Cell#: 290 – 4875